Literatura de Cordel collection, 1918-1995
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Profane Tales., 1918-1995.
  - Title: O rapaz que fugiu do morte e morreu Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista Place: Juazeiro do Norte, Ceará., 02/1977. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Title: Os retrocessos da sorte Author: Antonio Araújo de Lucena Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown Place: Campina Grande., 23/6/1977. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Title: O rico e o pobre Author: José Severino Cristovão Illustrator: signed VALERIO Publisher: J. S. Cristovão Place: Caruaru, PE., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Title: Historia do Ajapau Author: Silvino Pereira da Silva Illustrator: signed but illegible Publisher: Francisco Bandeira de Melo Place: João Pessoa., 1974. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Title: O cangaceiro Antonio Silvino Author: Alexandre José Felipe Cavalcanti d'Albuquerque Saboia Dila Illustrator: signed DILLA Publisher: Gráfica Felipe Saboia DILLA Place: Caruaru, Pe. Other: acrostic, JCDILLA., 12 de agosto de 1983. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Title: Os camponeses na queimada Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, COSTALEITE., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Cuidados ao aplicar dfensivos agrícolas Author: Enéas Tavares dos Santos Illustrator: signed ETS Publisher: Seção de Aperfeiçoamento Profissional e Treinamento da COONE, SECOM-COONE Place: Maceió, Al.., 10 de janeiro de 1981. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Part of the "Programa Nacional de Melhoramento da Cana-de-Açucar Coordenadoria Regional Nordeste" on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Câmara Cascudo Author: Otacilio Batista Illustrator: signed João 75 Publisher: Ind. Gráfica União Place: Natal., agosto de 1975. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: A carta do patrão e a resposta do vaqueiro Author: Chico Pedra Illustrator: signed AA Publisher: Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Norte Place: Natal, RN., 1980. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Castro Alves: o poeta dos escravos Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Illustrator: signed JRS Publisher: Eno Teodoro Wanke Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ., 1983. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: De como foi que Damásio veio governar com o povo Author: unknown Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: A União Cia. Editora Place: João Pessoa, PB., 1980. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: História de Cazuza Sátyro: o matador de onça Author: João Melquíades Pereira Illustrator: signed E. Lima Publisher: Casa das Crianças de Olinda Place: Olinda, PE., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: A história da menina que viveu duas veses Author: Manoel Pereira de Lima Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: História de páu fincado e barra limpa Author: Sandoval Pascoal Publisher: Laboratórios Edison Bezerra S. A. Place: Recife, Pernambuco., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Advertisement for Sangue Vita on rear wrapper.
  - Title: História de Jeca Tatú Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed J.BARROS Publisher: Tip. Pontes Place: Guarabira, Pb.., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Hydekel de Freitas: idealismo e trabalho, um ano de governo de 13 de maio de 82 a 13 de maio de 83 Author: Flavio Poeta F. Moreira Publisher: F. P. F. Moreira Place: Duque de Caixas, RJ., 30 de junho de 83. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: História de Olinda Author: Thales Galhardo Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: História de um poeta Author: Olívio Martins Viana Publisher: Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Norte Place: Natal, RN., 1980. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Sôbre os círculos operários de Pernambuco Author: Manoel Miguel Pereira Publisher: unknown Place: Gravatá, Pernambuco., 25 de março 1966. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Palavras de Getulio Vargas: uma luz para o futuro Author: Caetano Cosme da Silva Publisher: C. C. da Silva Place: Paulalho, Pernambuco Other: acrostic, CAETANO., 1900s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: As palhaçadas de Zé Pancinha Author: Francisco de Souza Campos Illustrator: signed J.B. Publisher: Universidade Federal de Pernambuco Place: Pernambuco Other: acrostic, F.SOUZA CAMPOS., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: As plantas fazem milagres Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: Fundação Casa das Crianças de Olinda Place: Olinda Other: acrostic, COSTALEITE., 1983. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Teatro Valdemar de Oliveira, Teatro de Amadores de Pernambuco Author: multiple authors Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., outubro 83. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: A morte dos quatro inocentes no Rio Grande do Norte Author: José Cordeiro Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: A candidatura de Getulio Vargas Author: Delarme [Monteiro??] Publisher: José Bernardo da Silva Other: acrostic, DELARME., 29/8/1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: A morte comanda o cangaço Author: Joaquim Batista de Sena Publisher: Manoel Caboclo e Silva Place: Juazeiro do Norte., 24/08/77. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Zé do Brejo, o caipora Author: José Soares Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: Casa das Crianças de Olinda Place: Olinda., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Caruaru nordeste Author: José Severino Cristóvão Publisher: Zacarias Barreto Place: Caruaru, PE Other: 6a. edição., ca. 1980s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Caruaru de ontem e de hoje Author: José Severino Cristóvão Illustrator: signed WALERIO Publisher: J. S. Cristóvão Place: Caruaru, PE., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Caruaru de ontem e de hoje Author: José Severino Cristóvão Illustrator: signed DILLA Publisher: J. S. Cristóvão Place: Caruaru, PE Other: 9o edição., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Os bandoleiros do vale do sol Author: João Vicente Emiliano Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, EMILIANO., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Batalhas dos Guararapes Author: Homero do Rêgo Barros Illustrator: signed MS Publisher: H. R. Barros Place: Recife, PE Other: acrostic, HOMERO., 1979. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O rapaz que brigou um ano e seis meses dentro de um cabaço Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: unknown Place: Condado, PE Other: acrostic, J.COSTA., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O reino do Principe Ribamar da beira fresca Authors: Edgley Ribeiro, Francisco Zênio Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown Place: Juazeiro do Norte, Ce. Other: acrostic, FZENIO EDGLEY., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Rogaciano Leite: o Castro Alves do seculo XX Author: Pedro Bandeira Publisher: P. Bandeira Place: Juazeiro do Norte, Ce.., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Fabiano Teimosia Author: Maria de Lourdes Teodoro Illustrator: signed Capai Alexandre Publisher: Gráfica Escola de Jornal e Artes do Sindicato dos Jornalistas Profissionais do DF Place: Brasília., 8 de maio de 1978. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Uma festa no sertão Author: José Bernardo da Silva Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: Tip. São Francisco Place: Juazeiro do Norte, Ceará., 1900s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Forças armadas, pátria e povo Author: Homero do Rêgo Barros Publisher: H. R. Barros Place: Recife., 1980. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O folheto da brigada em salgado de solânea Author: Antonio Patricio Publisher: unknown., 1977. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: As festa de Bezerros de outrora Author: Manoel Leite Filho Publisher: M. L. Filho Place: Bezerros, Pe.., 1900s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O fim do casa moreno Author: José Soares Publisher: unknown Place: Recife., 04/07/75. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Photo of Wilson Campos on front wrapper.
  - Title: Folheto dos ex-combatentes Author: José Gonzaga dos Passos Publisher: unknown Place: Jaboatão, PE., 1900s. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O cangaceiro Severino Batista de Morais Author: Alexandre José Felipe Cavalcanti d'Albuquerque Saboia Dilla Illustrator: signed DILLA Publisher: Gráfica Felipe Saboia Place: Caruaru, PE Other: acrostic, JCDILLA., after 1973. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: Camões e o rei mágico Author: José Cavalcanti e Ferreira Dila Illustrator: signed DILA Publisher: Gráfica Sabaó Place: Caruaru, PE Other: acrostic, JCFDILA., after 1950. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O cangaceiro colchete Author: José Cavalcanti e Ferreira Dila Illustrator: signed DILA Publisher: Gráfica Felipe Saboia Place: Caruaru, PE Other: acrostic, JCFDILA., after 1973. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Title: O canchimbo da confuzão Author: Luiz Gonzaga de Lima Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown., after 1940. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Mais um poeta nasceu Author: escrito por 40 poetas Publisher: João José da Silva Place: Recife, PE., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A moça que dançou com uma caveira Author: Francisco Sales Arêda Illustrator: signed JERONIMO Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: 15: a votação certeira pra prefeito João Moreira Author: Catalano Goiano do Brasil Publisher: Gráfica Walt Disney., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O cometa Halley vollta a terra depois de 76 anos Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Illustrator: signed Sinézio Alves 85 Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1985. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Camisinhas para todos Author: José João dos Santos (Azulão) Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, JAZULAO., after 1960. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: História do boi que falou em Minas Gerais Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ Other: acrostic, AALVES., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O barbeiro fofoqueiro Author: Hildemar de Araujo Costa Illustrator: José Costa Leite Publisher: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Arruda Câmara: idealismo e trabalho Authors: Expedito F. Silva, Cícero Vieira da Silva Publisher: E. F. Silva Place: Rio de Janeiro., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: ABC de Cocalinho Author: Luiz Nava Illustrator: Jussandir Raimundo de Sousa signed JRS Publisher: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Filho Place: Goiânia, Goiás., 1986. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Desafio de eleitor desiludido com votante esperanço Author: Zé Massa Publisher: unknown., 1980s. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Conselhos de um poeta Author: Nelci Lima da Cruz Publisher: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante., dezembro de 1984. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Certo bolo enfeitado Author: Nilton Manoel Publisher: unknown Place: Riberão Preto., 8/12/84. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O encontro da velha que vendia tabaco com o matuto que vendia fumo Author: João Parafuso Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: Gráf. Borges Place: Bezerros, PE., after 1940. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A intriga do cachorro com o gato Author: José Pacheco Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown., after 1940. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A filha de um pirata entre a espada e a sorte Author: Cicero Vieira Publisher: José Alves Pontes Place: acrostic, Guarabira Other: acrostic, CICERO VIEIRA., novembro de 1985. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Lampião de Vila Bela Author: José Perreira da Relva Dilla Illustrator: signed Sabóia Publisher: José Cavalcanti e Ferreira Dila Place: Caruaru, PE Other: acrostic, SABOIA., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Lire sublime dos imortais Author: Luiz Nava Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Place: Goiânia, Goiás., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O Brasil no mundo da inflação Author: Mariano Imperador Docílio Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: M. I. Docílio Place: Salvador, Bahia Other: acrostic, MARIANO., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: É triste o homem cair nas garras do alcoolismo Author: Severino Cesário da Silva Illustrator: signed JOAO Publisher: Fundação das Crianças de Olinda Place: Olinda Other: acrostic, CESARIO., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A mudança de Sarney e o futuro do Brasil Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1986. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Jânio Lima Fortes e João Alberto Lima Fortes, meus irmãos de poesia, sangue e canção Author: Fortes Sobrinho Publisher: MA e Arag. Go. Place: Conceição do Araguaia, Pará., 1988. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: I centenário da abolição da escravatura: 1888-1988, Princesa Isabel a redentora Author: Antonio José da Silva Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Aristóteles: o grande filósofo grego Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1985. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Viva o povo brasileiro! e João Valdo Ribeiro! Author: Lúcia Victória Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A radioatividade de Césio assombra Goiânia Author: Luiz Nava Illustrator: Sinézio Alves 88 Publisher: L. Nava Place: Goiânia, Goiás., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A vitória de Waldir Pires e a liberdade do povo bahiano Author: Antonio Lucena do Mossoró Publisher: A. L. Mossoró., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Vida, luta e morte do trovador Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Author: José Lara Publisher: Rodolfo Filho Place: Belo Horizonte, MG., ca. 1986. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Recordações do meu pai Rodolfo Cavalcante Author: Adolfo Moreira Cavalcante Illustrator: signed Sinezio Alves 87 Publisher: A. M. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Abolição da escravatura, 100 anos Author: Homero do Rêgo Barros Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: H. R. Barros Place: Recife, PE Other: acrostic, HOMERO., maio 1988. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Abolição...sim, discriminação...não Author: Lamartine Morais Illustrator: signed DILA Publisher: unknown., ca. 1988. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: ABC de Mário Filho Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: unknown Place: Recife, PE Other: 2a edição., 1988. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O ABC do jogo do bicho e suas revelações Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed J.BARROS Publisher: Gráfica e Editora Luana Ltda. Place: Duque de Caxias, RJ Other: acrostic, AALVES., setembro de 1985. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O ABC do feijão e os tumultos nas filas Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed MS Publisher: Tip. Pontes Place: Guarabira, Pb.., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O ABC da cachaça Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO 87 Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ Other: 2a edição., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: O drama do retirante Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: A Voz da Poesia Nordestina Place: Condado, PE., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Carybé o artista que se tornou baiano pela lei, pela arte e pelo povo Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: Fundação Cultural do Estado da Bahia Coordenação de Bibliotecas Other: acrostic, CARIBÉ., 1900s. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Carta aos trabalhadores da cana Author: unknown Publisher: Centro de Publicações CNBB, Regional Nordeste 2 Place: Recife, PE., setembro de 1981. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Amanhecer carioca Author: Manoel Messias Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: unknown Place: Vargem Grande, Rio., 10/2/87. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Veridiano Araújo e Carmosina e o amor ao teatro de bonecos Author: Manoel Santa Maria Publisher: unknown Place: Araruama, RJ., after 1984. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A briga da cana com o café Author: José Caetano da Silva Editor: Gutemberg Liberato de Andrade Collection: Caatinga Cearense No 5 Publisher: Artes Gráficas Chaves Ltda. Place: Fortaleza, Ceará., 05/10/82. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Cangaceiros Colchete e Jararaca Author: Alexandre José Felipe Cavalcanti d'Albuquerque Saboia Dilla Editor: Antony Cavalcanti e Ferreira Illustrator: signed DILLA Publisher: Literatura de Cordel São José Place: Caruaru, PE Other: acrostic, JCDILLA., after 1973. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: Cangaceiros e revoltosos Author: Alexandre José Felipe Cavalcanti d'Albuquerque Saboia Dilla Editor: Antony Cavalcanti Ferreira Illustrator: signed DILLA Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, FDILLA., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Title: A vitoria do Dr. João Durval Carneiro Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1982. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Vitória de Tancredo e o fim da ditadura Author: Manoel Basilio Publisher: unknown., after 1985. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Nova república de onde vem? pra onde vai? Author: Pedro Gomes Illustrator: Régis Soares signed Régisoares Publisher: unknown., ca. 1980s. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A luta da cidade de Olinda contra o avanço do mar Author: Fernando Gondim Publisher: unknown Place: Olinda., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Getúlio Vargas Author: Gonçalo Ferreira da Silva Publisher: unknown., after 1954. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Galileu Galilei: vida e obra Author: Gonçalo Ferreira da Silva Publisher: unknown., fevereiro 1988. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: O funrural vai piorar se a gente deixar... Author: unknown Publisher: Setor de Publicações CNBB Rigional Nordeste 2 Place: Recife, PE., maio de 1981. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: As grandes enchentes do nordeste 1985 Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed Ciro Publisher: Gráfica e Editora Dantas Ltda. Place: Duque de Caixas, RJ., maio de 1985. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: O Grande Rio Author: Nilton José da Silva Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Fundo de garantia do tempo de serviço: prejudica os trabalhadores rurais Author: unknown Publisher: Centro de Defesa dos Direitos Humanos, Serviço da Documentação e Informação Popular Place: Recife, Pernambuco., 1979. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Discussão do paraíba com o carioca Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed J.BARROS Publisher: Luana Artes Gráficas e Editora Ltda. Place: Duque de Caxias, RJ Other: acrostic, AALVES., maio de 1965. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A discussão do carioca com o pau-de-arara Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed but illegible Publisher: Luana Artes Gráficas e Editora Ltda. Place: Duque de Caxias, RJ., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Eleições direitas já para um novo presidente Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed JOEL Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ., 03/05/84. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Dr. Jorge Calmon grande jornalista brasileiro Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcanti Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Discussão dos três coronéis com Tasso Jereissati Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista Place: Juazeiro do Norte, Ceará Other: 6a edição., 18/10/1986. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A despedida do João e a vitória de Tancredo Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: Gráfica e Editora Dantas Ltda. Place: Duque de Caxias, RJ., janeiro de 1985. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Deus fala palavra eterna pra ontem, hoje, amanhã Author: unknown Publisher: Centro de Defesa dos Direitos Humanos, Serviço de Documentação e Informação Popular Place: Recife, PE., setembro 1983. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Corre Campo Author: Alexandre José Felipe Cavalcanti d'Albuquerque Sabaó Sabóia Illustrator: signed Autor Sabóia Publisher: So Cordel São José Place: Caruaru, PE Other: acrostic, SABOIA., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A volta do vaqueiro Author: Francisco Pedra Illustrator: signed but illegible Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A contagiosa AIDS matando a humanidade Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed Ciro Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic, AALVES., abril de 1987. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Constituição e Constituinte Author: Manoel Alves de Sousa Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: unknown Place: Araruama, RJ., março de 1986. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Castro Alves não morreu vive na alma do povo Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 12 de março de 1985. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Castro Alves e Camões: dois gênios da poesia universal Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Illustrator: signed JRS Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1984. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Hildemar de Araújo Costa: um poeta da Bahia Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: unknown., 1986. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Quando Rodolfo partiu Author: João Crispim Ramos Publisher: Feira de Santana, Bahia Other: acrostic, JOÃOCRAMOS., novembro de 1986. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Brizola quer tocar fogo no bigode de Sarney Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ., after 1960. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: O matador de onças Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: Tip. Pontes Place: Guarabira, Pb. Other: acrostic, COSTALEITE., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Leonilda Hilgenberg Justus: a patativa canora do Paraná, mulher poesia Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: R. C. Cavalcante Place: Salvador, Bahia., 1984. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A vida do velho barreiro Author: Gonçalo Ferreira da Silva Publisher: unknown., julho 87. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Santos-Dumont o pai da aviação Author: Gonçalo Ferreira da Silva Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: O menino da porteira Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed J.BARROS Publisher: Tip. Pontes Place: Guarabira, Pb.., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: História e martírios da escrava Anastácia Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro Other: acrostic, AALVES., 11 de 01 de 85. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: As maravilhas do Rio de Janeiro Author: Zacarias Jerônimo da Costa Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown Place: Rio de Janeiro Other: acrostic, ZACARIAS., 1900s. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Manoel Salviano prefeito de Juazeiro Author: Medeiros Illustrator: signed STÊNIO Publisher: unknown Place: Juazeiro do Norte, Ceará., 26/01/88. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A luta de Lampião para entrar no inferno Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ Other: acrostic, AALVESS., 27/10/84. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A prescrição bienal, ou, O lei dos 2 anos Author: unknown Illustrator: Marcelo Soares signed MS Publisher: unknown., maio 1979. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: Prefeitura nos bairros: Jarbas e sua equipe de governo descentralizando e decidindo juntos Author: João José da Silva Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: Prefeitura da Cidade do Recife Place: Recife., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: É povo no centro Author: João José da Silva Illustrator: José Costa Leite Publisher: Prefeitura da Cidade do Recife Place: Recife., 1987. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: O poeta e a cigana Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: Tip. Pontes Place: Guarabira, Pb. Other: acrostic, AALVES., after 1950. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: O pavoroso incêndio do edifício andorinha no Rio de Janeiro Authors: Apolônio Alves dos Santos, Flávio Fernandes Moreira Publisher: Luana Artes Gráficas e Editora Ltda. Place: Duque de Caxias, RJ., 1986. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Voting recommendations on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Parque Histórico Castro Alves Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: unknown., 14 de março de 1984. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Title: A nova constituição e a voz do presidente Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Place: Rio de Janeiro, RJ., julho de 1985. (Box 20, Folder 2)